Guide to the David Plowden Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1948-2011; Series I; 189; 41.9 linear_feet
  - July 1995 Acquisition
    - Reproducible Prints and Study Prints
      - Former Soo Line Railroad ore Dock. Manguette, Michigan (975) Reproducible print, 1975 September (Box 109)
      - Freight House Door, Pennsylvania Railroad Depot. Falls Creek, Pennsylvania (No Number Extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 October (Box 109)
      - Funnel Detail, Ann Arbor Railroad # 7, Lake Michigan Railroad Car Ferry. Frankfort, Michigan (MI-963-43) Reproducible (plus) print, 1963 September (Box 109)
      - Interior Ferryboat Scranton, Hoboken Ferry, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad. Hoboken, New Jersey (EL-1167-1008) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 109)
      - Joint Southern Pacific-Western Pacific Railway Station. Beowawe, Nevada (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 109)
      - Norfolk Western Railway Coal Train. Near Pocahontas, Virginia (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1974 (Box 109)
      - Open-Pit Copper Mine. Bisbee, Arizona (678-638) Reproducible (plus) print, 1978 June (Box 109)
      - Side of box Car, Naperville Junction Railway at Delaware Hudson Railroad Freight Yard. Oneonta, New York (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, 1975 (Box 109)
      - Smoke Stack and Wheelhouse, Tugboat Julia C. Moran. New York, New York (JCM) Reproducible (plus) print, 1974 (Box 109)
      - Staircase on Side of Store. Waterville, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1973 October (Box 109)
      - Sternwheel, Steamer Delta Queen, Mississippi River. Rock Island, Illinois (964-647) Reproducible (plus) print, 1964 September (Box 109)
      - Tank Farm. Near Dubuque, Iowa (881-897) Reproducible (plus) print, 1981 August (Box 109)
      - "Tapping the heat", Open Hearth Furnace, Steel Mill. East Chicago, Indiana (IS-1599) Reproducible (plus) print, 1979 (Box 109)
      - TSS Princess Marguerite, Canadian Pacific Railway. Port Angeles, Washington (GFB-68-5887) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 109)
      - Unfinished Freeway. Atlanta, Georgia (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 109)
      - View from Bedroom, 157 East 75th Street. New York, New York (478-78) Reproducible print, 1978 April (Box 109)
      - Water Pump, Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad. Thurmond, West Virginia (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 109)
      - Abandoned Grain Elevator. Dallas, South Dakota (969-727) Reproducible (plus) print, 1969 September (Box 110)
      - Café Window. Lanark, Illinois (969) Reproducible (plus) print, 1969 September (Box 110)
      - Casino Café. La Crosse, Wisconsin (CP-No Number) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 110)
      - Chicago, Illinois (881-1039) Reproducible (plus) print, 1981 August (Box 110)
      - Chicago, Illinois (1079-29) Reproducible (plus) print, 1979 October (Box 110)
      - Chicago, Illinois (1079-221) Reproducible print, 1979 October (Box 110)
      - Doorway. Galena, Illinois (CP-No Number) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 (Box 110)
      - Florence, Arizona (678) Reproducible (plus) print, 1978 (Box 110)
      - Ganargua Creek Aqueduct (WC-1134) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 (Box 110)
      - Golconda, Nevada (CP-No Number) Study print, 1973 (Box 110)
      - Grain Elevator. Antelope, Montana (GP) Reproducible (plus) print, 1977 (Box 110)
      - Holyoke, Massachusetts (CP-No Number) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 (Box 110)
      - Lauren. Presque Isle, Michigan (680-687) Reproducible (plus) print, 1980 June (Box 110)
      - Main Street. Edina, Missouri (CP-No Number) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 (Box 110)
      - Main Street, North Side. Cazenovia, New York (NYS-366-35) Reproducible print, 1966 March (Box 110)
      - Mohawk, New York. Mohawk, New York (1073) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 October (Box 110)
      - North of Union Station. Chicago, Illinois (1079?) Reproducible (plus) print, 1979 October (Box 110)
      - Main Street Apache, Oklahoma (969-476) Reproducible (plus) print, 1969 September (Box 110)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad Freight Station. Falls Creek, Pennsylvania (1066) Reproducible (plus) print, 1966 October (Box 110)
      - Post office. Ogallah, Kansas (CP-1941) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 110)
      - U.S. Route 93. South of Wells, Nevada (CP-1782) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 110)
      - Whitman County, Washington (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 110)
      - York, North Dakota (CP-No Number) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 (Box 110)
      - Abandoned Church. Midland City, Illinois (473) Reproducible print, 1973 April (Box 111)
      - Bloomfield Bridge. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1967 May (Box 111)
      - Bloomingdale's. Manhasset, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1974 January (Box 111)
      - Calumet River Bridges Including Chicago Skyway Bridge. Chicago, Illinois (HDP-1066) Reproducible print, 1966 October (Box 111)
      - Captain Cornelius Steevels, Senior Captain, Hoboken Ferry, in Wheel House Ferryboat Elmira, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad, Last year of Operation. Probably New York, New York (EL-467-99) Reproducible print, 1967 April (Box 111)
      - Church Window. Forest City, Pennsylvania (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1973 May (Box 111)
      - Grain Elevator. South Chicago, Illinois (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1979 (Box 111)
      - Grain Elevator. Superior, Wisconsin (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 111)
      - Grain Elevator. Superior, Wisconsin (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 111)
      - Grain Elevators. Golden Valley, North Dakota (GP) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 111)
      - Grain Elevators. North Topeka, Kansas (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1968 October (Box 111)
      - Headstone. Snyder, Oklahoma (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1969 September (Box 111)
      - Housing Project. Waukegan, Illinois (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1979 (Box 111)
      - Indian Reservation. Cache Creek, British Columbia, Canada (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 111)
      - Looking East from Ohio Street, Chicago River. Chicago, Illinois (1078-193) Reproducible print, 1978 October (Box 111)
      - The Mid-Hudson Bridge. Poughkeepsie, New York (GFB-469) Reproducible (plus) print, 1969 April (Box 111)
      - New York Central Railroad Steam Tugs, Hudson River. North Weehawken, New Jersey (ST-NYC-363-32) Reproducible print, 1963 March (Box 111)
      - Old Trails Bridge, Colorado River. Topock, Arizona (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 111)
      - R. H. Birkhead, Agent M-K-T Railroad on the Day of his Retirement after 60 (sixty) Years Service. Frederick, Oklahoma (GFB-68-3426) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 111)
      - Steve. Davy, West Virginia (374-1889) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 111)
      - Union, Logan County, Illinois (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1973 April (Box 111)
      - View from a Holiday Inn. Phoenix, Arizona (678-834) Reproducible print, 1978 June (Box 111)
      - Abandoned Farm House. Near Lincoln Valley, North Dakota (GP-1975) Reproducible (plus) print, 1971 (Box 112)
      - Approaching 98' Meridian. Steele County, North Dakota (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1968 July (Box 112)
      - Approaching 98' Meridian. Steele County, North Dakota (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1968 July (Box 112)
      - Binghamton, New York. Binghamton, New York (BING-566) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 112)
      - Block Island, Rhode Island (BI-473-169) Reproducible print, 1973 April (Box 112)
      - Bosler, Wyoming (874) Reproducible print, 1974 (Box 112)
      - Butte, Montana (CP-No Number) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 112)
      - Car in Front of Laundromat. Gotebo, Oklahoma (969-387) Reproducible print, 1969 September (Box 112)
      - Coxsackie, New York (1073) Reproducible print, 1973 October (Box 112)
      - Doorway. Block Island, Rhode Island (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 112)
      - Eldridge, North Dakota (372) Reproducible print, 1972 (Box 112)
      - Fayetteville, West Virginia (374-724) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 112)
      - Galena, Illinois (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 112)
      - Gas Pump. Hazelton, North Dakota (GP) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 112)
      - Main Street. Perryville, Missouri (874) Reproducible print, 1974 (Box 112)
      - Main Street. Marion, Kansas (CP-623) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 112)
      - Queen Anne Style Home. Newark, New York (WC-00?) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 112)
      - Sea Cliff, New York (174) Reproducible print, 1974 (Box 112)
      - Site of Abandoned Grocery Store. Grenville, New Mexico (471-367) Reproducible print, 1971 April (Box 112)
      - Staircase on Side of Store. Waterville, New York (1073) Reproducible print, 1973 October (Box 112)
      - Stewart's Garage. Cement, Oklahoma (969-463) Reproducible print, 1969 September (Box 112)
      - Wayne County Court House. Lyons, New York (WC-007) Reproducible print, 1966 (Box 112)
      - Wheat Fields. Near Dusty, Washington (CP-1194) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 112)
      - American Thread Company. Willimantic, Connecticut (475) Reproducible print, 1975 April (Box 113)
      - Barn. Algiers, Vermont (V-NH-865) Reproducible print, 1965 August (Box 113)
      - Barn. Clare County, Michigan (975) Reproducible print, 1975 September (Box 113)
      - Barn. Near Angola, La Graye County, Indiana (969) Reproducible print, 1969 June (Box 113)
      - Bluefield, West Virginia (374-1941) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 113)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, 4-6-2 Type Steam Locomotive, Number 1262. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-1202) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 113)
      - Former Milwaukee Railroad Depot. Waterloo, Wisconsin (880-118) Reproducible print, 1980 August (Box 113)
      - Hostler Washing Locomotive. McAdam, New Brunswick, Canada (CPR-McAdam) Reproducible print, 1959 July (Box 113)
      - Houses by Former New Haven Railroad Tracks. Putnam, Connecticut (475-705) Reproducible print, 1975 April (Box 113)
      - License Plates, Side of Barn. Clare County, Michigan (975-2439) Reproducible print, 1975 September (Box 113)
      - Looking toward Bethlehem Steel Works, Blast Furnaces. Johnstown, Pennsylvania (785-450) Reproducible print, 1975 August (Box 113)
      - New Bedford, Massachusetts (475) Reproducible print, 1975 April (Box 113)
      - Newark, New Jersey (NJ-164) Reproducible print, 1964 (Box 113)
      - Philipsburg, Montana (CP-2040) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 113)
      - Power Canal and Mills. Lawrence, Massachusetts (1174-299) Reproducible print, 1974 November (Box 113)
      - Reading Company, Outer Station. Reading, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-83) Reproducible print, 1963 October (Box 113)
      - Steam Locomotive 5145, Canadian Pacific Railway. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-5145) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 113)
      - Westbound Freight Train, Great Northern Railway. West of Havre, Montana (GFB-68) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 113)
      - [Statue of Liberty from Caven Point Road]. Jersey City, New Jersey (467-1018) Reproducible print, 1967 April (Box 114)
      - 80 " Hot Strip Mill Finishing Stands (IS-2111) Reproducible print, 1979 (Box 114)
      - Allouez Ore Docks. Superior, Wisconsin (679-624) Reproducible print, 1979 June (Box 114)
      - "Bat" Nelson, Barber (age 91 years). Alta Vista, Kansas (591-329) Reproducible print, 1991 May (Box 114)
      - Bathroom Hotel Brooklyn. Brooklyn, Iowa (687-452) Reproducible print, 1987 June (Box 114)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway Steam Locomotive #5145. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-5145) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 114)
      - Carla Sleeper, Hartman School. South Haven, Michigan (992-1359) Reproducible print, 1992 November 9 (Box 114)
      - Charging Open Hearth Furnace (IS-1479) Reproducible print, 1979 (Box 114)
      - Chicago, Illinois (181-56) Reproducible print, 1981 January (Box 114)
      - Chicago, Illinois (1078-193) Reproducible print, 1978 October (Box 114)
      - Church. Saline County, Missouri (874-528) Reproducible print, 1974 August (Box 114)
      - Coat Room Hartman School. South Haven, Michigan (992-154) Reproducible print, 1992 September (Box 114)
      - Coxsackie, New York (1073-118) Reproducible print, 1973 October (Box 114)
      - Detail Farmers Co-op Grain Elevator. Dike, Iowa (1083-627) Reproducible print, 1983 October (Box 114)
      - Dysart, Iowa (686-1687) Reproducible print, 1986 June (Box 114)
      - East of Las Vegas, New Mexico (471-179) Reproducible print, 1971 May (Box 114)
      - Engineer Oiling Steam Locomotive. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360) Reproducible print, 1960 March (Box 114)
      - Farmstead. Will County, Illinois (481-2) Reproducible print, 1981 April (Box 114)
      - Firehold S.T. Crapo. Probably Muskegon, Michigan (989-698) Reproducible print, 1989 September (Box 114)
      - Former Lackawanna Railroad Station. Scranton, Pennsylvania (PA-164-292) Reproducible print, 1964 (Box 114)
      - Frank Morris, Roll Tender. Chicago, Illinois (C-1183 36) Reproducible print, 1983 November (Box 114)
      - General Store. Cedar Bluff, Iowa (287-188) Reproducible print, 1987 (Box 114)
      - Grain Elevator. North Topeka, Kansas (GFB-68-4850) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 114)
      - Grain Elevators. Golden Valley, North Dakota (GP-257) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 114)
      - Great Northern Rly, Westbound Freight Train. West of Havre, Montana (GFB-68-1344) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 114)
      - Hoboken Ferry Terminal. Hoboken, New Jersey (NYH-FB/DL-168) Reproducible print, 1960 (Box 114)
      - Housing Development in Wheat Field. Pullman, Washington (CP-454) Reproducible print, 1973 (Box 114)
      - Indian Reservation. Cache Creek, British Columbia, Canada (GFB-68-4569) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 114)
      - Joe McKay, Fireman, Steamer S.T. Crapo(1190-320) Reproducible print, 1990 November (Box 114)
      - Longview Bridge, Columbia River. Longview, Washington (GFB-68-1857) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 114)
      - LTV Corp (Jones Laughlin Steel). East Chicago, Indiana (IS-2532) Reproducible print, 1979 (Box 114)
      - Mid-Hudson Bridge. Poughkeepsie, New York (GFB-69-109) Reproducible print, 1969 (Box 114)
      - Moe Dickey, Horse-trader. Eleven Mile Corner, South Dakota (GP-602) Reproducible print, 1971 (Box 114)
      - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (PB-567) Reproducible print, 1967 May (Box 114)
      - R.H. Birkhead, Station Master, Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad, on the Day of His Retirement After 60 Years with the Railroad. Frederick, Oklahoma (GFB-68-4826) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 114)
      - Reading Co. Outer Station, Scale. Reading, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-30) Reproducible print, 1963 October (Box 114)
      - "Scoopers" in Hold of steamer William A. McGonagle. Buffalo, New York (785-1062) Reproducible print, 1985 July (Box 114)
      - Scoopers in Hold of William A. McGonagle. Buffalo, New York (1085-384) Reproducible print, 1985 October (Box 114)
      - South 10th Street Bridge. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (PB-567-1264) Reproducible print, 1967 May (Box 114)
      - State Line Generating Station and Abandoned Malt House by Conrail Tracks. South Chicago, Illinois (C-483-478) Reproducible print, 1983 May (Box 114)
      - Steamer Crispin Oglebay Loading Coal at Norfolk Southern Rly Coal Dock. Sandusky, Ohio (890-671) Reproducible print, 1990 August (Box 114)
      - Steamer J. Burton Ayers(1090-543) Reproducible print, 1990 October (Box 114)
      - Steamer Kinsman Independent at International Multi-Foods Elevator. Duluth, Minnesota (685-544) Reproducible print, 1985 June (Box 114)
      - Steamer Kinsman Independent Unloading Cement Clinker. Superior, Wisconsin (685-994) Reproducible print, 1985 June (Box 114)
      - Steel Mill East Chicago, Indiana, Slagging Ingots. East Chicago, Indiana (IS-1574) Reproducible print, 1979 (Box 114)
      - Steve. Davy, West Virginia (374-1889) Reproducible print, 1974 March (Box 114)
      - Super Market Shopping Center. Beaver Dam, Wisconsin (481-470) Reproducible print, 1981 April (Box 114)
      - The Western House. Springville, New York (892-743) Reproducible print, 1992 August (Box 114)
      - Wesley Chapel. Near Henderson, Mills County, Iowa (487-286) Reproducible print, 1987 April (Box 114)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, Locomotive #1262. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-57) Reproducible (plus) print, 1960 March (Box 115)
      - Colorado Southern Railroad. Grenville, New Mexico (471-452) Reproducible print, former exhibition print, 1971 April (Box 115)
      - Corn Crib in Soy Bean Field. Near Grand Junction, Greene County, Iowa (686-1102) Reproducible (plus) print, 1986 June (Box 115)
      - Coxsackie, New York (1073-118) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 October (Box 115)
      - Crosshead Detail 0-6-0 Type Locomotive, Union Transportation Company. New Egypt, New Jersey (UTC-1959-10) Reproducible (plus) print (Box 115)
      - CSX Railroad, Railroad Yard. Presque Isle, Toledo, Ohio (685-2196) Reproducible (plus) print, 1985 June (Box 115)
      - Face on Back of Turbine, State Line Generating Plant, Commonwealth Edison Co. Chicago, Illinois (C-1083-31) Reproducible (plus) print, 1983 October (Box 115)
      - Former Chicago Eastern Illinois Railroad Depot. Princeton, Indiana (1066-63) Reproducible print, former exhibition print, 1966 October (Box 115)
      - House. Deep River, Iowa (386-221) Reproducible (plus) print, 1986 March (Box 115)
      - Housing Development. Pullman, Washington (CP-454) Reproducible (plus) print, 1973 (Box 115)
      - Locomotive Driving Wheels, Canadian Pacific Railway 2-8-2 Number 5145, St. Luc Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360) Reproducible (plus) print, 1960 March (Box 115)
      - Maurice Stroda's Garage. Ramona, Kansas (591-1640) Reproducible (plus) print, 1991 May (Box 115)
      - Shopping Mall, Easter Sunday Morning. Beaver Dam, Wisconsin (481-470) Reproducible (plus) print, 1981 April (Box 115)
      - Soo Line Depot. Martin, South Dakota (GFB-68-2100) Reproducible (plus) print, 1968 (Box 115)
      - Steamer S. T. Crapo, Inland Lakes Management, Leaving Waukegan, Thanksgiving Day, Last Trip of Season. Waukegan, Illinois (1185-21) Reproducible (plus) print, 1985 November (Box 115)
      - Thomas Viaduct. Baltimore Ohio Railroad. Relay, Maryland (LFC-688) Reproducible (plus) print, 1964 (Box 115)
      - [Tyrone Bridge]. Tyrone, Kentucky (GFB-68-630) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Anchorage, The Wire Bridge, Carrabassett River. North New Portland, Maine (GFB-69-1806) Reproducible print, 1969 (Box 116)
      - Bollaron Truss, Former B O Railroad, 2 Through Spans over Patuxent River. Savage Factory, Maryland (467-185) Reproducible print, 1967 April (Box 116)
      - Boston Maine Railroad, Connecticut River, Lattice Truss. Northampton, Massachusetts (GFB-68-3094) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Bridge over Musconetcong, Light Foot Pratt Pony Truss. New Hampton, New Jersey (GFB-469-481) Reproducible print, 1969 April (Box 116)
      - Brooklyn Bridge. East River, New York (173) Reproducible print, 1973 January (Box 116)
      - The Brooklyn Bridge. East River, New York (173-90) Reproducible print, 1973 January (Box 116)
      - The Brooklyn Bridge, Brooklyn Tower. East River, New York (173-64) Reproducible print, 1973 January (Box 116)
      - The Brooklyn Bridge (Brooklyn Tower). East River, New York (173-203) Reproducible print, 1973 January (Box 116)
      - The Brooklyn Bridge, Brooklyn Tower. East River, New York (173-200) Reproducible print, 1973 January (Box 116)
      - The Brooklyn Bridge, Brooklyn Tower. East River, New York (173-107) Reproducible print, 1973 January (Box 116)
      - The Cincinnati-Newport Bridge or Central Bridge, Ohio River. Between Cincinnati, Ohio, and Newport, Kentucky (GFB-68-735) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - The Covington and Cincinnati Suspension Bridge, Ohio River, John A. Roebling, Engineer (GFB-68-512) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Delaware River Highway Bridge, Mitonville, Pennsylvania, Looking Towards Skinner's Falls, New York. Between Mitonville, Pennsylvania and Skinner's Falls, New York (GFB-69-1192) Reproducible print, 1969 (Box 116)
      - Delaware River Bridge. Between Mitonville, Pennsylvania and Skinner's Falls, New York (GFB-69-774) Reproducible print, 1969 (Box 116)
      - Detail of Steel and Ribs, Eads Bridge, Mississippi River. Saint Louis, Missouri (GFB-68-4341) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - The Delaware Aqueduct, Delaware River, John A. Roebling, Engineer. Lackawaxen, Pennsylvania (570-86) Reproducible print, 1970 May (Box 116)
      - Former 6th Street Bridge over Allegheny River, Now Spans Back Channel of Ohio River. Coraopolis, Pennsylvania (PB-567-1646) Reproducible print, 1967 May (Box 116)
      - Former 6th Street Bridge over Allegheny River, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, at Time of Photograph (5/67) Crossed Back Channel of Ohio River at Coraopolis, Pennsylvania. Coraopolis, Pennsylvania (PB-567-1454) Study print, 1967 May (Box 116)
      - Former Boston Maine Railroad Bridge, Connecticut River, Completed 1887. Northampton, Massachusetts (GFB-68-4267-4) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Former Boston Maine Railroad Bridge, Connecticut River. Northampton, Massachusetts (GFB-68-3098) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Former Boston Maine Railroad Bridge, Connecticut River. Northampton, Massachusetts (GFB-68-6224) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Former Highway Bridge over Mississippi River between Clinton, Iowa and Fulton, Illinois (GFB-68-1230) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Former New York Central Railroad (Putnam Division) Bridge over New Croton Reservoir. Westchester County, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 116)
      - Highway Bridge, Delaware River. Between Mitonville, Pennsylvania and Skinner's Falls, New York (GFB-69-600) Reproducible print, 1969 (Box 116)
      - Kinzua Viaduct, abandoned, Now a State Park. North of Mount Jewett, McKean County, Pennsylvania (GFB-68-16) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - The Kinzua Viaduct. North of Mount Jewett, McKean County, Pennsylvania (GFB-68-24) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - The Kinzua Viaduct. North of Mount Jewett, McKean County, Pennsylvania (GFB-68-28) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - The L N Bridge, Ohio River. Between Cincinnati, Ohio and Newport, Kentucky (GFB-68-698) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - The L N Bridge, Ohio River. Cincinnati, Ohio (GFB-68-662) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - The L N Bridge, Ohio River. Between Cincinnati, Ohio and Newport, Kentucky (GFB-68-586) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Marietta Bridge, Ohio River. Williamsport, West Virginia (GFB-68-1247) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Muscatine Bridge, Mississippi River. Muscatine, Iowa (GFB-68-2763) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - The Muscatine Bridge, Thrust Cantilever and Simple Truss, Mississippi River, built 1890. Muscatine, Iowa (GFB-68-1640) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - The Muscatine Bridge, Mississippi River. Muscatine, Iowa (GFB-68-2764) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Nebraska City Bridge, C B O Railroad, Missouri River. Nebraska City, Nebraska (GFB-68-5159) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Nebraska City Bridge, Missouri River (GFB-68-5153) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Nebraska City Bridge, Missouri River (GFB-68-3624) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Newport-Cincinnati Bridge, Ohio River (GFB-68-734) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)
      - Phoenix Bridge Company, Bowstring Truss, Oil Creek. Oil City, Pennsylvania (GFB-68-1870) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 116)